<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/activity_about_us"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".AboutUs"
    android:background="@color/colorPurple">

    <RelativeLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_marginLeft="5dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="5dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
        android:background="@color/colorlightPurple">


        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="25dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="30dp">

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical"
                android:layout_marginTop="6dp">


                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_gravity="center"
                    android:layout_marginLeft="8dp"
                    android:text="Ranglerz Digital Marketing"
                    android:textColor="@color/colorWhite"
                    android:textSize="22dp"
                    android:gravity="center"
                    android:textStyle="bold"/>

                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginLeft="8dp"
                    android:layout_marginRight="8dp"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:textColor="@color/colorWhite"

                    android:text="Thank you for your interest. We’re full-fledged IT Solution Provider Company based in Newcastle Peterborough: England, Belgium, and in Lahore: Pakistan. We create professional websites, social networks, brands and high-performance web applications for clients of all shape and sizes (from large blue-chip corporations, job portals, property portals to international musicians, DJs, cosmetics, health sites etc.). Ranglerz endeavor to provide the most effective, innovative and practical solutions in developing each project into a success story. We are proud to provide high quality, reliable, dependable, flexible, and very user-friendly web sites for non-commercial and commercial organizations together with excellent customer support. We are the specialists in Website Design, e-Commerce, Graphic Designing, Pay Per Click i.e. Google Advertising, Social Media Marketing i.e. Facebook Marketing, Search Engine Optimization and Mobile Applications Development (Android, IOS).

Formed in the winter of 2012 by lifelong brothers, from its humble beginnings as a little-big idea, Ranglerz Digital Marketing has grown through the years into the dynamic development team it is today.

Our services are scalable, so we can address the needs of businesses of all sizes. Companies ranging from innovative startups to well established companies with eight-digit revenue make use of our technical expertise, with an emphasis in developing projects in Php, Cake Php, Html, html5, WordPress, Joomla, Microsoft .NET, Java, Oracle, Unity, Android, IOS etc.

To see what Ranglerz Digital Marketing can do for you, visit our Portfolio page or Contact Us to obtain a quote today!"/>




            </LinearLayout>

        </ScrollView>

    </RelativeLayout>





</RelativeLayout>
